<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flash Software on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/</link><description>Recent content in Flash Software on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:04:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Preparations</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/preparations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:05:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/preparations/</guid><description>Download and install the Arduino IDE. Start the Arduino IDE, go to File &amp;gt; Preferences. At Additional Board Manager ULRs enter https://raw.githubusercontent.com/spacehuhn/hardware/master/wifiduck/package_wifiduck_index.json. You can add multiple URLs, separating them with commas. Go to Tools &amp;gt; Board &amp;gt; Board Manager, search for wifi duck and install WiFi Duck AVR Boards and WiFi Duck ESP8266 Boards. Download and extract this repository or git clone it. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find the COM port of ESP8266 board, then you&amp;rsquo;re probably missing the right drivers.</description></item><item><title>Flash Atmega32u4</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/atmega/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:06:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/atmega/</guid><description>Open atmegaduck/atmega_duck.ino with the Arduino IDE. Under Tools &amp;gt; Board in the WiFi Duck AVR section, select your board; for example, Sparkfun Pro Micro. Connect the Atmega32u4 board via USB and select its port under Tools &amp;gt; Port. [Optional] Under Tools you can enable the LED and set its pin. You can also change the USB ID to make it appear as a certain type of keyboard. Press Upload. Unbrick Atmega32u4</description></item><item><title>Flash ESP8266</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/esp8266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:07:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/software/esp8266/</guid><description>Open esp_duck/esp_duck.ino with the Arduino IDE. Under Tools &amp;gt; Board in the WiFi Duck ESP8266 section, select your board. For example NodeMCU 1.0 (ESP-12E Module). Connect the ESP8266 board via USB and select its port under Tools &amp;gt; Port. Press Upload. Pro Tip: If the ESP8266 is already running this software and you just want to update it, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to connect it via USB. You can update it over the air!</description></item></channel></rss>