<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Supported Devices on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/</link><description>Recent content in Supported Devices on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 22:29:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dstike Boards</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/dstikeboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 22:44:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/dstikeboards/</guid><description>If you want to support the development of this project, you can buy one of the offical boards by DSTIKE (Travis Lin) on following sites:
DSTIKE.com 🇨🇳 Tindie 🇨🇳 AliExpress 🇨🇳 Taobao 🇨🇳 Maltronics 🇬🇧 The Deauther boards come preflashed with the Deauther software and don&amp;rsquo;t require the installation process.
They are made especially for this project and come with a sharp 1.3 inch OLED screen, external antenna and 18650 battery connector.</description></item><item><title>Node MCU</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/nodemcu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 22:55:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/nodemcu/</guid><description>This is the recommended board for beginners that want to learn more about electronics and programming!
The NodeMCU is an open source project and there are many companies producing it. The most known one is Amica. There is also a Lolin NodeMCU v3 but don&amp;rsquo;t get confused by any version number:
I always recommend the v1.0 (might be sold under a different version number). It&amp;rsquo;s the board from Amica. It is cheap, breadboard friendly and uses the cp2102, a better alternative to the old CH340 USB to serial chip.</description></item><item><title>Wemos &amp; Adafruit</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/wemos_adafruit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 23:11:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/wemos_adafruit/</guid><description>Wemos D1 mini The Wemos boards have decent quality, are cheap and very small.
They work just like a NodeMCU and you can get a variety of addon shields for them!
But you have to be careful, there are a lot copies of the Wemos products!
Adafruit HUZZAH ESP8266 Adafruit has a Feather board with the ESP8266 in their sore. Those are a bit more pricy than the chinese NodeMCUs but you get a very quailty board in return, good online documentation and a friendly community around it.</description></item><item><title>Fake Boards</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/fakeboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 23:08:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/supporteddevices/fakeboards/</guid><description>You will find some cheaper boards that look like the official deauther boards but for lower prices. I highly recommend to stay away from them!
These companies like to copy Travis Lin&amp;rsquo;s (DSTIKE) designs, use my software and sell it as seemingly official Wemos boards!
Recently they started to label their boards as &amp;ldquo;TTGO&amp;rdquo;. They don&amp;rsquo;t put much effort into it, so the quality is often horrible and the PCB design very poor.</description></item></channel></rss>