<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup Display &amp; Buttons on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/</link><description>Recent content in Setup Display &amp; Buttons on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 16:57:24 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tools</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 16:59:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/need/</guid><description>Before you continue Using the display interface is completely optional.
The ESP8266 Deauther can also just be used over serial or the web interface.
You should know some basics of how to use, code and create stuff with Arduino.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t, then we highly recommend you to get some sort of Arduino starter kit and start learning. The steps of this tutorial are very simple, but if you have never done something like this, it&amp;rsquo;s very important to get a basic knowledge about the topic first!</description></item><item><title>Adjust code</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/adjust/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:24:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/adjust/</guid><description>Now that your setup is done, you have to make some changes to the code.
See Installation on how to compile and upload code using Arduino.
Open Arduino and go to A_config.h (second tab)
Change all the #define settings according to your setup. The default settings are for the I2C example setup, just without the Neopixel LED. Be sure not to confuse the GPIO pins with the NodeMCU pins (D0,D1&amp;hellip;)! You can find the NodeMCU pinout above.</description></item><item><title>Testing</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/testing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:26:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/setup/testing/</guid><description>Now when everything is correctly setup and uploaded, you have to open the serial monitor with arduino.
Make sure to set the baud rate to 115200 and select Newline.
If you see that the device is resetting every few seconds, check the code! Most of the time it&amp;rsquo;s that you used one pin for both the display, button or LED.
Be sure not to have used the same pin for multiple things, not on the breadboard and not in the code!</description></item></channel></rss>