<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ESP8266 Deauther on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/</link><description>Recent content in ESP8266 Deauther on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 17:39:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/faq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:28:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/faq/</guid><description>How to ask a question I recommend you watch THIS video before you post a new issue to ask something.
Timeout error A typical message you get in the web interface is the red ERROR timeout loading file ... message.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry!
It tells you that a transmission in the background failed.
This can happen because:
The ESP8266 web server is just randomly unreliable (nothing you can do here, just try again or use the OLED and buttons) The WiFi around is very crowded and transmissions are not reliable because of the high traffic (try changing the channel in the settings and restart, or use it in a less crowded area) You started an attack and the ESP8266 had to change the channel (you might have to reconnect manually) You&amp;rsquo;re scanning for stations (you can reconnect once the scan is finished) You&amp;rsquo;re attacking multiple targets and the ESP8266 has to change the WiFi channel constantly (you will have to restart to reconnect) The ESP8266 crashed - in this case, please look at Serial usage for further debugging.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:00:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/projects/</guid><description>A collection of cool projects people made with the ESP8266 Deauther.
I hope this gives some inspiration and motivation to make/hack something together yourself :)
If you have cool projet that isn&amp;rsquo;t listed here, let me know to add it by tweeting me @spacehun!
Deauthing Sandals Drone Hacking a FAKE Makerspace Deauther Magnet Box for Fridge Deauth Detector with 10W RGB Pwned the pwner Deauthing Sandals Becky Button @einsteinunicorn in collaboration with Naomi Wu @RealSexyCyborg designed and 3D printed a sandal.</description></item><item><title>Serial Commands</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/commands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:30:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/commands/</guid><description>Serial Commands Suggest changes Source</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/settings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:28:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/settings/</guid><description>Settings Suggest changes Source</description></item><item><title>Writing Scripts</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/scripts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:01:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/deauther/scripts/</guid><description>Introduction One cool thing about the new deauther version is the ability to write scripts. This is meant as a small add-on, and not as a main feature. You can&amp;rsquo;t really program with it or do complicated stuff, and all you can do is save regular commands to a file. To show you this, I will demonstrate how to deauth a specific mac address using a script. The only caveat here is that you need to know the channel.</description></item></channel></rss>