<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WiFi Duck on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/</link><description>Recent content in WiFi Duck on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 17:39:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:03:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/about/</guid><description>By emulating a USB keyboard, this device can be used to remote control a computer, automate tasks or execute software to gain full access. All in the matter of seconds!
This is all possible because keyboards are trusted devices, you plug it in and can start typing right away!
A human might not type very fast, but an automated device like this presses of hundreds of keys per second.
This open source project aims to provide a user-friendly tool to learn about such keystroke injection attacks.</description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 18:33:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/disclaimer/</guid><description>This is a tool.
It&amp;rsquo;s neither good nor bad.
Use it to do good, to study, and to test.
Never use it to do harm or create damage!
The continuation of this project counts on you!
&amp;nbsp;I have a question &amp;nbsp;Suggest changes &amp;nbsp;Source</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/faq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/faq/</guid><description>&amp;nbsp;What&amp;#39;s new compared to the WiFi Ducky? Changes since the WiFi Ducky predecessor include:
Support for multiple keyboard layouts No size limit per script (other than the physical memory limit) No line length limit for the STRING command Faster typing speed Optional Neopixel or Dotstar LED Entirely new web interface Support for I2C to enable easier debugging and DIY builds &amp;nbsp;I forgot the password Flash the ESP8266 again, but make sure that you select Erase Flash: Sketch + WiFi Settings under Tools in the Arduino IDE.</description></item></channel></rss>