<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on Spacehuhn Wiki</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on Spacehuhn Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:31:43 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ducky Script</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/duckyscript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:34:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/duckyscript/</guid><description>Basics Keys are separated by a single space.
Everything written in a single line gets pressed and released at the same time. To write text, use the STRING function.
Example Explanation WINDOWS r Type the Windows key and then the r key WINDOWS r Press the Windows key and the r key simultaneously STRING WINDOWS r Write WINDOWS r Functions Command Example Description REM REM Hello World!</description></item><item><title>CLI</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/cli/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:35:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/cli/</guid><description>The command line interface or CLI is accessible using a serial connection to the ESP8266 (115200 baud, Newline ending) or via the web interface at 192.168.4.1/terminal.html.
General Command Description Example help Returns all available commands help ram Returns available memory in bytes ram version Returns version number version settings Returns list of settings settings set -n/ame -v/alue Sets value of a specific setting set ssid &amp;quot;why fight duck&amp;quot; reset Resets all settings to their default values reset status Returns status of i2c connection with Atmega32u4 status run &amp;lt;&amp;hellip;&amp;gt; Starts executing a Ducky script run example.</description></item><item><title>Debug</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/debug/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:37:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/debug/</guid><description>To properly debug, you need to have both the Atmega32u4 and the ESP8266 connected via USB to your computer.
That can be tricky when you only have a all in one board, so it might be useful you built one yourself. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to solder it, for example you can use an Arduino Leonardo and a NodeMCU and connect them with jumper cables.
Now open 2 instances of Arduino (so they run as separate processes!</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/faq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://spacehuhn.wiki/wifiduck/usage/faq/</guid><description>If you have a question, you can check out the issue section.
Use the search function to look up similar questions, be sure to check both open and closed issues!
Also watch this video by LiveOverflow on &amp;ldquo;How (not) to ask a technical question&amp;rdquo;.
I forgot the password Flash the ESP8266 again, but make sure that you select Erase Flash: Sketch + WiFi Settings under Tools in the Arduino IDE.</description></item></channel></rss>